ANNA GOETZ



CONTACT

(v) Snoveien 10, 1363 Høvik

P +47 912 66 500

anna.gtz087@outlook.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ anna-goetz-29294b199/

https://annagtz2022.github.io/ portfolio_AS/

EDUCATION

Master's in Economics of enterprise, 2015

Odessa National Polytechnic University, Ukraine

Bachelor's in Metallurgy, 2012

National Metallurgical Academy of Ukraine

SKILLS

- Research and analysis
- Problem-solving
- Customer-centric mindset
- Continuous learning
- Efficient work practices
- · Meticulous attention to detail
- Dynamic work environment
- Advanced in Excel (incl. Power Pivot), PowerPoint
- · Familiar with SQL, Power BI, and Python
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills

LANGUAGES

English fluent Ukrainian native Russian native

HOBBIES













Logistics Coordinator

ABOUT ME

I am a versatile professional with a diverse skill set and extensive experience in various areas, including financial product sales, management, research, data analysis, and visualization. My proactive approach, enthusiasm, rapid learning ability, and adeptness in navigating high-pressure environments have consistently contributed to exceeding targets, leading to frequent promotions and increased responsibilities. I possess exceptional communication skills and have honed my ability to build trusted relationships with people from various backgrounds.

EXPERIENCE

Embassy of Ukraine in the Kingdom of Norway | 2022-2023 **Humanitarian Operations Assistant, Volunteer**

I prepared shipping documents, tracked aid donations and shipments in spreadsheets, and calculated the value of humanitarian aid.

Infosystem Center LLC | Odessa, Ukraine | 2019 Information and communication network operator

I assisted users with software functionality and effectively addressed claims between clients and drivers, providing comprehensive support and resolving any issues that arose.

PLASKE PJSC (cargo company) | Odessa, Ukraine | 2017-2018 **Accountant**

I accurately recorded and oversaw financial transactions, collaborating with cross-functional teams to ensure the timely and accurate delivery of relevant data for daily operational evaluations. Additionally, I effectively managed payment accounts and maintained financial balance between systems.

PLASKE PJSC (cargo company) | Odessa, Ukraine | 2015-2017 **Office Support Specialist**

I was responsible for end-to-end order handling, support process optimization, handling service contracts (including supplier research, evaluation and selection), budget planning, invoice processing, office supply and equipment management, and its inventory audits. Through meticulous research and comprehensive data analysis of office expenses and processes, I successfully identified valuable cost-saving opportunities and improved process efficiency. Additionally, I maintained open lines of communication with vendors and stakeholders to ensure smooth operations, and promptly resolving issues.

Consumer Center LLC (loan center) | Odessa, Ukraine | 2014-2015 Department manager

Managing customer accounts, and training and supervising new employees to provide high-quality service have helped me consistently exceed sales revenue targets. Additionally, I maintained office policies and procedures, managed equipment inventory, and ensured efficient office operations. I also maintained accurate records of all funds and was primarily responsible for their collection.

Delta Bank JSC | Yalta, Crimea, Ukraine | 2011-2014

Account manager

I efficiently manage clients' accounts, providing them with financial advice and effective solutions, while also processing transactions with utmost accuracy. I have consistently demonstrated a strong ability to build and foster enduring client relationships, leading to their continued loyalty and satisfaction. This ability have helped me surpassing sales revenue targets, and have resulted in my achievement of being one of the top three performers among bank branches.

| ANNA GOETZ

Logistics Coordinator



4 July 2023

Snoveien 10, 1363 Høvik

| +47 912 66 500

CONTACT

anna.gtz087@outlook.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ anna-goetz-29294b199/

https://annagtz2022.github.io/ portfolio_AS/

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality

(A) Ukrainian

Date of birth

3 01.06.1987

Marital status

(n) Married

REFERENCES

Available upon request

Please feel free to browse my portfolio.

https://annagtz2022.github.io/portfolio_AS/



Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing to express my keen interest in the Logistics Coordinator position at Aker Solutions. One aspect that particularly excites me about joining Aker Solutions is the opportunity to work on a wide variety of projects and contribute to solving global energy challenges. The prospect of actively participating in the ongoing digitization process and developing innovative logistics solutions aligns perfectly with my career aspirations.

Throughout my career, I have gained extensive experience in various areas such as financial product sales, department management, operational efficiency, research, and analysis. For example, I have performed supplier evaluation and selection, managed office supplies, processed invoices, oversaw equipment inventory, and conducted budget planning. I maintained open lines of communication with vendors and stakeholders to ensure smooth operations, promptly addressing concerns and resolving issues. Additionally, I identified cost-saving opportunities and improved process efficiency. My proactive approach, enthusiasm, curiosity to acquire new knowledge, rapid learning ability, and adeptness in navigating high-pressure environments have consistently contributed to exceeding targets, leading to frequent promotions and increased responsibilities.

Having lived in Ukraine and Austria (2019-2021) before relocating to Norway in January 2022, I appreciate diverse cultures and possess excellent communication and interpersonal skills. My volunteer experience at the Embassy of Ukraine in the Kingdom of Norway and translation work for the Historical Museum have honed my organizational, analytical, and language skills, as well as attention to detail.

I am a holder of a residence card in Norway, and I bring a proactive, curious, positive mindset, and a result-driven approach to every challenge. I am confident that my diverse background, strong problem-solving and analytical skills, commitment to self-improvement, and strong interest in technology, customs handling, and process optimization will enable me to quickly grasp new concepts and software to make a valuable contribution to the Aker Solutions' team.

Thank you for considering my application. I look forward to the opportunity to discuss my qualifications further with you.

Sincerely,

Anna Goetz